reversephonelookup.com 2018-07-22

# Privacy policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for ReversePhoneLookup.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of having your information included in this directory. You can do this at any time by visiting our removal form and requested your information be removed.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

**Cookies and Tracking**  
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
